http://www.huggableteddies.com/privacy-policy-1

HomeShopHat SizingIn Memory OfTERMS & MORERETURNSTERMS & CONDITIONSSHIPPING PRIVACY POLICYMoreHomeShopHat SizingIn Memory OfTERMS & MORERETURNSTERMS & CONDITIONSSHIPPING PRIVACY POLICYHomeShopHat SizingIn Memory OfTERMS & MORE Privacy PolicyWe respect our customer’s privacy.  In this policy “we” or “us”refers to HMAEA Creations, LLC.  Information is collected from you when you register on the website, place an order, e-mail communications, or mailing lists, as well as orders placed on mobile devices.When ordering or registering, we ask you for your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information, as well as any other information needed.You may also place orders over the telephone by contacting us at 419-708-0102.Sensitive and private data collected on our site happens over a SSL encryption which transfers sensitive information from your web browser to our databases.Use of informationThe information you provide us is to help us respond to your order, process payments, and take care of any support or requests to give you the best customer service.We also use this information for our promotions that maybe on our site.We may also use your email address to send updates regarding your order, inquires, questions, or updates related to our products.We do not sell or rent your name or personal information for use by any outside companies or third parties.Web Browser CookiesWe use “cookies” so we may enhance customer experience. Cookies are used to receive information on browse type, and capture certain information such as the web pages you click. This helps us compile data about our site traffic, and interaction which helps us offer a better shopping experience.You can choose to turn off all cookies.  Please visit the help portion of your internet browser.Who we share data withWe may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting in fraud prevention or investigation.  This would only be done as necessary to comply with legal requirement, to protect against or prevent actual and to prevent potential fraud, unauthorized transactions, or investigating fraud which has already taken place.Changes to Privacy PolicyHMAEA Creations, LLC has the discretion to change our privacy policy, and we will revise those changes on this page.  Check this page to stay informed.  Policy modified September 24, 2017. Copyright © 2019  HMAEA Creations, LLC - All Rights Reserved.
